<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>IR on Jonathan Chin</title>
    <link>https://shimmering-seahorse-8e7553.netlify.app/tags/ir/</link>
    <description>Recent content in IR on Jonathan Chin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 17:29:52 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://shimmering-seahorse-8e7553.netlify.app/tags/ir/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Post-1949 US-China Relations: A (Very) Brief Overview</title>
      <link>https://shimmering-seahorse-8e7553.netlify.app/posts/third/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 17:29:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shimmering-seahorse-8e7553.netlify.app/posts/third/</guid>
      <description>This post hopes to provide a brief overview of post-1949 US-China relations. While I do think/hope much of the analysis presented is accurate and nuanced, do note that many ideas and key events (e.g., 1989 Tiananmen) are left out. I&amp;rsquo;ve chosen what to include based on a personal judgement of how significant and interesting ideas or events are in understanding the relationship!
US-China relations occupy a distinct and significant position in modern international relations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The International Criminal Court and Africa (II)</title>
      <link>https://shimmering-seahorse-8e7553.netlify.app/posts/second/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 00:36:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shimmering-seahorse-8e7553.netlify.app/posts/second/</guid>
      <description>The motivation for this two-part write-up originated in competitive debate, where ICC-Africa relations were a frequent topic of discussion. An international relations seminar course I took in first year gave me the opportunity to write a policy brief on the issue, from which this write-up is inspired. In Part 1, I dive into the history of the relationship between the ICC and Africa to set a context to a discussion on the present and future in Part 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The International Criminal Court and Africa (I)</title>
      <link>https://shimmering-seahorse-8e7553.netlify.app/posts/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2022 00:30:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shimmering-seahorse-8e7553.netlify.app/posts/first/</guid>
      <description>The motivation for this two-part write-up originated in competitive debate, where ICC-Africa relations were a frequent topic of discussion. An international relations seminar course I took in first year gave me the opportunity to write a policy brief on the issue, from which this write-up was conjured. In Part 1, I dive into the history of the relationship between the ICC and Africa to set a context to a discussion on the present and future in Part 2.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
